

NILADRI CHAKRABORTY

Data Scientist with 6 months experience in building data-intensive application, overcoming complex architectural and scalability issues in diverse industries. Proficient in predictive modelling, data processing, and data mining algorithms, as well as scripting language, including Python and JAVA.

☑ E-mail: bcaniladri@gmail.com

D Mobile:- 8250529528, 09434522344

V KOLKATA, WEST BENGAL

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/niladri-chakraborty-30685a1a/

EDUCATION

- *Completed Master of Computer Application (MCA) from Haldia Institute of Technology, HALDIA (2008-2011) under W.B.U.T. with DGPA 7.99.
- *Completed Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) under Burdwan University with 60%.
- *Completed HS Under WBCHSC with 42% in 2005.
- *Completed Madhyamik Under WBBSE with 61% in 2003.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PGT Computer Science Teacher

St. Xavier's High School

2/05/2023- Till Date

DAV PUBLIC SCHOOL

18/08/2022-29/04/2023

St. Xavier's High School

06/04/2015-16/04/2022

Technical Consultant

ECIL Rapiscan Ltd, Kolkata

DEC 2011- July 2014

*MySQL database Maintenance.

Training Details:

Advanced Certification Data Science & Artificial Intelligence- CCE IIT Madras and Intellipaat

Last one year I learn lot of things and completed project from Intellipaat.

Projects.

- 1. Netflix Recommendation Engine
- 2. Walmart Sales Prediction
- 3. Census Income Project

GENERAL SKILLS

Data Visualization Machine Learning Deep Learning Database Structures & Algorithms NumPy Pandas, Matplotlib Power BI SQL Python

TECHNICAL SKILL

Technical Languages: Python, JAVA, J2EE (JDBC,

JSP, Servlet), HTML, C++, CSS

Scripting Language: JavaScript, JQUERY.

Database/Server: Oracle, MYSQL, SQL Server

Development Tools (IDE): Eclipse, Netbeans,

Python IDLE, Jupyter, Google Colab

PROJECTS

Analyzing the trends of COVID-19

- * Importing COVID19 dataset and preparing it for the analysis by dropping columns and aggregating rows.
- * Merging two datasets and finding correlations among our data.
- * Visualizing our analysis results using Seaborn.

Flight Booking Price Prediction

The objective is to analyze the flight booking dataset obtained from a platform which is used to book flight tickets

CERTIFICATES

Advanced Certification Data Science & Artificial Intelligence- CCE IIT Madras and Intellipaat

(January 2022- Till Date)

INTERESTS





